

JORDAN ALEXIS

Junior Programmer and Designer

Brooklyn, NY 11212

alexisjordan842@gmail.com

16466258972

As a programmer, I can make websites, video games, and computer networks from scratch.

As a designer, it gave me many years of learning about how the field of my occupation works. I have used many applications at my disposal to create graphic arts like Adobe InDesign, Photoshop, XD, and Illustrator.

Using different programming languages, I publish websites on GitHub, Wix, WordPress, and use programs like Unity, Game Maker, Maya, Unreal Engine to make and produce games.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Spring Intern

WBAI Radio 99.5FM NYC -

Brooklyn, NY January 2019 to May 2019

- · Assisted in Sorting and Mailing out prizes for their WBAI Buddies.
- Managed their Social Media Using Hootsuite
- · Assigned managing some Customer Service tasks.
- Assisted in their event calendar by using Photoshop to make the pictures for each article presentable.
- Assisted in entering important personal data for their WBAI Buddies.

Multimedia Internship

SYEP, The Challenge Publisher Group - Brooklyn, NY

July 2018 to August 2018

Assisted in creating a modernized version of a newspaper called "The New American" by making it in Adobe InDesign from scratch.

- Used Photoshop to make images given to me more presentable.
- Distributed the Newspaper to the boroughs of New York.

Multimedia Developer Internship

SYEP, St. John's Recreation Center - Brooklyn, NY

July 2017 to August 2017

- Learned about Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, and InDesign effectively.
- Learned how to record audio using GarageBand and using audio to create a 3-5-minute video using Windows Media Player.

Day Care Worker

SYEP, Charles Churn Christian Academy - Brooklyn, NY

July 2014 to August 2014

- Assisted making sure the children (5-10) went to their destinations safely.
- · Assisted in making activities, organized the work and camp environment.
- Carried equipment to wherever they needed to be.

SKILL SET

COMPUTER SKILLS

- Intermediate Knowledge of Adobe Photoshop, InDesign, Illustrator, Premiere Pro, and XD.
- Understanding and Translating computer data, proficiency in cloud computing, IT, basic audio production.
- Intermediate knowledge of creating and designing websites.
- Have intermediate skills in Microsoft Word, Excel, and PowerPoint.
- · Have basic knowledge using Social Media.

EDUCATION

Bachelor's in Science, Major: Multimedia Computing and Computer Systems

Brooklyn College - Brooklyn, NY August 2019 to Present

Associates in Science, Major: Multimedia Programming and Design

Borough of Manhattan Community College (BMCC) - Manhattan, NY August 2017 to May 2019

Credits towards Associates Networking Technology Degree

Technical Career Institute (TCI) - Manhattan, NY January 2017 to May 2017

Credits towards Associates Computer Information Systems (Game Design Concentration)

Bramson Ort College - Queens, NY October 2014 to January 2017

LINKS

http://jordan721.github.io/Jordan Alexis

http://www.linkedin.com/in/jordan-alexis-799214175

https://www.facebook.com/jordan.alexis.l

https://www.instagram.com/jordan.alexis.l/